Hi there Lady J here, we are getting ready to mold some chocolates.
Chocolate, que rico.
Ok so prepping the molds.
So you buy your molds, you are going to want to wash. That's kind of common sense. There's some people out there that need that reminder.
Wash your molds, you never know who's been touching the molds and you know, we won't go there.
So I actually sometimes will get really lazy, I'll be honest, a little surprise, surprise.
I'll get lazy sometimes after I've made some chocolate and I've molded some chocolate, I will, my molds my plastic actually doesn't look all that dirty but it has some remnant, I'll give you an example, of left over, my last project you know, left over chocolate.
Example number one right there.
Can you see that chocolate?
No you can't see that chocolate.
Let me show you a little bit closer, can you see that chocolate, that left over chocolate, oooo yeah.
You know what before you get started make sure that your molds are washed.
After you wash them, you are going to want to dry them.
So I'm going to take a minute here and I'm going to go wash my molds and we will be right back to talk to you guys about a few different ways to do it.
But then we are going to show you guys how we are going to do it today with our sweet little bottle right here.